>> Brian Holt: 因此，让我们先谈谈 TypeScript 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So let's just talk
about TypeScript for a second.
首先这就是 React 和 React
First of all, this is going to
be specifically how React and
TypeScript 相交。
TypeScript intersect.
所以当我要解释 TypeScript 的时候
So while I'm going to be
explaining TypeScript as I go,
FrontendMasters 上有来自 Mike North 的完整的 TypeScript 课程
there is a full TypeScript course from
Mike North on FrontendMasters and
迈克是个伟大的老师
Mike's a great teacher.
我以前和他在 LinkedIn 一起工作所以如果你需要更深入的话
I used to work with him at LinkedIn and
so if you need like a more in depth
引入和探究 Mike的课程是一个很棒的开始。
introduction and delve into that Mike's
course is a great place to get started.
那么，什么是 TypeScript，为什么我要使用它。
So what is TypeScript,
why do I wanna use it.
对于这些问题的回答，为什么有用。
Why is it useful with react this
answer some of those questions.
所以我要在这里打开一个新的文件，然后再开一个。
So if I have I'm just gonna open a new
file here and closes for just a second.
我要把这个放进去换语言模式 TypeScript
And I'm gonna put this in,
Change Language Mode, TypeScript.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，如果我在此处有一个变量，那么变量 x = 5，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So if I have a variable
here that says var x = 5, right?
然后我说， x.toUpperCase()， >> Brian Holt: 现在
And then I say, x.toUpperCase(),
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now,
通常 JavaScript 是很酷的我会给你机会的
normally JavaScript's like cool,
I'll give that a shot.
就像你不知道那样会不会正常对吧
Like you have no idea if that's
gonna work or not, right?
你和我能看出来这是个数字
You and I can see right away
that this is a number and
这个肯定没有两个大写，对吧 ?
this definitely doesn't have
a two UpperCase, right?
> > Brian Holt: 但是 TypeScript 会对你大喊，说嘿，白痴，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But TypeScript is
gonna yell at you and say hey, idiot,
就像号码没有两个 UpperCase
like number doesn't have a two UpperCase.
这是一个很简单的例子，对吧 ?
Now this is a very simplified case, right?
但这将会使我们无法在运行时因类型而产生错误，对吧 ?
But this is going to save us from run time
production errors because of types, right?
现在我可以做的是我可以说
Now what I could do here
is I could say that and
一下子就好了这就行了吧
all of a sudden, okay that's a string,
that's gonna work, right?
这就是各种类型的东西，可以把你从这里拯救出去。
So these are the kinds of things that
types of going to save you from.
它会把你从电话中省下来
It's gonna save you from calling
to application a number it's
把你从呼叫 UpperCase 来救你
gonna save you from calling toUpperCase,
right.
这事很容易但它会说嘿， toUpperCase 不是件事
That's an easy one to do but it's gonna
say hey, toUpperCase isn't a thing.
你是说我是你的意思吗谢谢
Did you mean toUpperCase I did, thank you.
你可以说，换个拼写，它只会为你解决。
And you can actually say, change
spelling it will just fix it for you.
就像那种 TypeScript 能做的很酷的事情
Like there's some pretty cool stuff like
that that TypeScript can just do for
你会自动的
you automatically.
但在我看来如果我说 X 点就好了
But in my opinion, one of the better
parts about this if I just say x dot,
我甚至不用再看 MDN 了
right I don't even have
to look at MDN anymore.
它马上就出现在我的编辑中。
It just immediately appears in my editor.
就像嘿我们还是分开吧
It's like hey, let's do split and
那么我得弄清楚分割器是什么
then well,
I need to figure out what the splitter is.
我们去吧，对吧，然后我就会好了
Let's do /, right, and
then I'm gonna do, okay,
有多少人是我想做的对吗
how many of them do I want to do, right?
当我写代码时它会把我的文件给我
And it's giving me in line
documentation as I'm writing code,
就像那个神奇的权利一样
like that's magical right.
或者就像我从宠物/宠物中进口宠物一样
Or let's just say like I import
pet from afrontendmaster/pet.
这是一个你不知道的 API ，我知道是我写的，对，但你不知道。
This is an API that you don't know, I know
it cuz I wrote it, right, but you don't.
但我只能说宠物点好吧好吧
But I can just say pet dot,
okay, well cool.
那么让我们来看看动物，我能有什么样的堂堂堂堂堂堂堂堂堂堂堂堂们呢 ?
So let's get animals and
what kind of params can I have?
所以我可以放，我可以给它性别，组织，大小，
So I can put, well I can give it gender or
organization or size,
但是我们一起去， >> Brian Holt: 让我们按类型搜索。
but let's go with like,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's search by type.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，我们把猫放在那儿，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
we'll put cat there, right?
好了现在我在找猫然后如果我打了点就好了
Okay, so now I'm searching by cat and
then if I hit dot that's like okay,
这是一个承诺好吗
well this is a promise, okay?
那是干净的数据
That's neat and then data.
我不知道数据是什么但我们会花很多钱的对吧
I don't know what data is, but
we're gonna take a lot at it, right?
然后我会说数据，动物，动物或分页，
And then I'll say data.,
animals, animals or pagination,
然后动画好吧这看起来是个阵列吧
and then animals., okay,
this looks like this is an array, right?
因此，每一个动物都是如此。
So forEach and then animal.
Animalal，好吧，这可以有年龄和颜色
Animal., okay, so
this can have age and colors and
描述，这就像关于飞行的交互式文档，对吧 ?
description and this is like interactive
documentation on the fly, right?
这太酷了我连码头都不去看了
This is so cool that I don't even have to
look at the docs anymore, and, Joke's on
你，我没有写文件，所以没有文档去看，对吧 ?
you, I didn't write any documentation,
so there is no docs to look at, right?
这就是你的一切
So this is all you get.
> > Brian Holt: 但我只能在指尖处得到这些东西，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But I get all this
just at my fingertips, right?
如果我试着说 " 动物 " 我不知道
And if I try and say animal.,
I don't know, what's
你可能会想到的东西，腿，对吧 ?
something that you might think,
legs, right?
这并不是一件事情，它会说，嘿，这不是件事。
That's not really a thing,
it's gonna say, hey, that's not a thing.
你不能这样做，或者这是另一个有用的方法。
You can't do that or
this is another way this could be helpful.
还有一个叫做动物的 API 。
There is another API called animal.
如果我说动物，然后说点，那就会对我感到不安了。
If I say animal and then say dot then
it's gonna be upset at me because.
就像这个东西需要一个身份证
It's like, hey, this thing requires an ID,
如果你不给它身份证就不起作用了吧
if you don't give it an ID
then this doesn't work, right?
所以就有这么多的东西
So there's just a bunch of stuff
like this that it's gonna do for
你的幕后主使那些你之前从未想过的事情
you behind the scenes, stuff that you
would have never thought about before.
它和视觉演播室的代码很有效果，因为，让我告诉你，
And it just works beautifully with visual
studio code because, let me just tell you,
我坐在视觉上做你的代码团队，而 TypeScript 团队就在其中，
I sit with the visuals to do your code
team, and the TypeScript team is across,
大厅对吧
the hall, right?
所以他们只是不停地在大厅里相互叫嚷
So, they're just constantly yelling each
other back and forth across the hall.
你最喜欢的视觉效果是你的代码来自
So, a lot of your favorite features in
visuals to do your code are coming from
TypeScript 团队的实际情况。
the TypeScript team actually.